[{"answer": " This party seems pretty cool", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 11, "question": "", "qSentId": 10},{"answer": " Yeah, there must be 60 people here", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 12, "question": " This party seems pretty cool", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Do you want to get a drink?  I saw they have a keg out back, or we can mak", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 13, "question": " Yeah, there must be 60 people here", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Lets get a beer", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 17, "question": " Do you want to get a drink?  I saw they have a keg out back, or we can mak", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Lets get a beer", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " So, did you hear about what happened to Anne this week", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 19, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " No what happened", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 20, "question": " So, did you hear about what happened to Anne this week", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Her car got stolen", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 21, "question": " No what happened", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " What?  Really?  Where was it", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Her car got stolen", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " It was just parked outside of her apartment.  She woke up in the morning and i", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 23, "question": " What?  Really?  Where was it", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Did she call the police", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 29, "question": " It was just parked outside of her apartment.  She woke up in the morning and i", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " Yeah, she didOh my god  look over there", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Did she call the police", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " What", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Yeah, she didOh my god  look over there", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Its that guy from my Chemistry class.  He is so hot.  I have a crush on him.  ", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 32, "question": " What", "qSentId": 31},{"answer": " You mean the guy over in the corner with the blue shirt", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Its that guy from my Chemistry class.  He is so hot.  I have a crush on him.  ", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Yes.  Dont let him see you looking", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 37, "question": " You mean the guy over in the corner with the blue shirt", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " I know him.  Thats Matt", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Yes.  Dont let him see you looking", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Really", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 39, "question": " I know him.  Thats Matt", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Yeah, hes my friend Pauls friend.  Lets go over there.  Ill introduce you", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Really", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " I dont know.  Do I look OK", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Yeah, hes my friend Pauls friend.  Lets go over there.  Ill introduce you", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Yes.  Now, come on.  Lets go meet him", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 42, "question": " I dont know.  Do I look OK", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Hi, Matt.  How are you", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Yes.  Now, come on.  Lets go meet him", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Meredith, hey.  Whats up", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Hi, Matt.  How are you", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Not much.  This is my friend, Lisa", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 45, "question": " Meredith, hey.  Whats up", "qSentId": 44},{"answer": " Hey, Lisa.  Nice to meet you", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Not much.  This is my friend, Lisa", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Hi", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Hey, Lisa.  Nice to meet you", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Im just going to run to the bathroom.  You guys talk, and Ill be right back", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Hi", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " So, how do you know Meredith", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Im just going to run to the bathroom.  You guys talk, and Ill be right back", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " I know her though Paul, a mutual friend of ours.  What about you", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 50, "question": " So, how do you know Meredith", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " We met in a class last year.  Speaking of classes, I think youre in my Chemistr", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 51, "question": " I know her though Paul, a mutual friend of ours.  What about you", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Oh, yeah.  I thought you looked familiar.  How do you like the class", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 55, "question": " We met in a class last year.  Speaking of classes, I think youre in my Chemistr", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Oh, it's so boring.  Im practically asleep every day", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 56, "question": " Oh, yeah.  I thought you looked familiar.  How do you like the class", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " Me too.  I thought I was the only one", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Oh, it's so boring.  Im practically asleep every day", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " No, its definitely boring", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Me too.  I thought I was the only one", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " So, what are you majoring in?  Chemistry", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 62, "question": " No, its definitely boring", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " No way.  Im a French major.  Im just taking Chemistry to fill the universit", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 63, "question": " So, what are you majoring in?  Chemistry", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Me too.  Im a Spanish major", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 67, "question": " No way.  Im a French major.  Im just taking Chemistry to fill the universit", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " Thats cool, so I guess we both like languages", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Me too.  Im a Spanish major", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " Yeah.  Actually, there is a foreign film fest this weekend.  Would you like to g", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Thats cool, so I guess we both like languages", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " Saturday?  Sure.  Id love to", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 73, "question": " Yeah.  Actually, there is a foreign film fest this weekend.  Would you like to g", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " OK, great.  Let me get your number and then Ill call you Friday, and we ca", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 74, "question": " Saturday?  Sure.  Id love to", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " OK, its 706-652-9987", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 78, "question": " OK, great.  Let me get your number and then Ill call you Friday, and we ca", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " Got it.  Listen, I gotta run, but Ill call you", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 79, "question": " OK, its 706-652-9987", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " Sure, talk to you later", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 80, "question": " Got it.  Listen, I gotta run, but Ill call you", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Hey, Im back.  So how was talking with Matt", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 81, "question": " Sure, talk to you later", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " You wont believe this, but he asked me out.  We have a date", "docId": "10-05", "aSentId": 82, "question": " Hey, Im back.  So how was talking with Matt", "qSentId": 81}]
